With my little sister Ashley.
So, we are on section three, and as you can see, when I go back I actually may start to do this over.
I told you earlier that it was a little loose, as you can see that hair's a little bit loose.
So, depending upon how long you want the hair to last, you may want to redo that if it look loose like that.
Okay, so I have, I'm still doing the same technique, I'm doing a crossover like that but while you were away I kind of switched my hands a little bit, there's other techniques that I won't show you right now, but, alright, so my hand is holding my middle finger, my pointer finger is holding the bottom one.
I've got my pointer finger and my thumb holding another, and I've got basically my fingers back here holding on to, with my hand, the third tuft.
So in one hand I've got three tufts of hair right here.
Now with my other hand, what am I going to do?
I'm going to grab some more hair and I'm going to put it underneath on the lower one, and then cross over, bring this under.
That's that difference between a cornrow and French braid, is you bring it under.
With that under one, I'm going to add some more hair, and switch hands.
Bring the top one under, and what am I going to do with it?
Add some hair.
Switch the sides, so grab it with your hand.
What are the next fingers that grab?
It's the one that just went under, top, then under.
Okay, grab some more hair, add it to the bottom one, switch sides, put that one in your hand.
Where does this top one go?
It goes right here and then this one goes on the bottom.
Okay, what am I going to do next?
Grab some more hair, and that process just goes over, if you'll see, and over and over again, okay?
Grab it with your hand.
The next one, and then the next one, just like that.